Finding Aid for the June Wayne Papers LSC.0562
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1942-1997
  - Subseries 2: Dorothy Kline, 1909-1981
    - Dorothy-- Letters TO, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      Includes: Handwritten notes from Wayne's daughter, Robin Wayne, to Dorothy Kline; letter from Edgar Kadden (Chicago, IL) to Dorothy (1960 June 1); get well card from Claire and Robert Blaskovitz (Claire's Corset Shop, Chicago, IL) (1960 June 27.)
    - Music, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      Includes: List of song titles, composers and publishers used in Wayne's "The Dorothy Series"; sheet music for "My Melancholy Baby" and "September Song."
    - CHICAGO, 1909, 1917, 1924, 1931, 1950-1962 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      Includes: Printed microfilm page from New York Times (1931 September 20) with article, "Jobless Women in Parks"; photocopies from the Chicago Historical Society of photographs by Mildred Mead of Chicago street scenes where Wayne's family lived, including Lake Park Avenue, Cable Court, Kimbark Avenue, and Spaulding; also contained guide book, "Rand McNally Guide to Chicago and Environs," (Chicago, 1924), removed to UCLA Special Collections.
    - Kline Family Documents, 1955, 1960, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      Includes: Certified copy of Dorothy Kline's death certificate; letter from Dr. Lester M. Morrison to J.W. Cohen (accountant, Chicago, IL) re determination of Florence Kline's health status (1955 August 18); photocopy of coroner's certificate of death for Florence Kline (1961 April 4.)
    - June: Original Documents, 1930, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      Includes: Avondale School certificate for services of June Kline [Wayne] as Monitor on the Avondale Junior Patrol, signed by Gertrude S. Pease (1930 June); Wayne's passport application (1957?)
    - Al Lavine, 1917, 1949, 1956, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      Includes: Empty glassine envelope with note re photo blow up of Abe Lavine; photographic enlargement and photocopies of wedding portrait of Wayne's parents, Abe [Albert] Lavine and Dorothy Kline; handwritten letters from Abe Levine (1949, 1956); 3 x 5 inch sepia-toned photograph of Lavine (1939 October); business card for Albert Lavine, Fire and Police Commissioner; 4 x 5 inch black and white negative and photograph of Lavine's business card; photocopies of death certificate (certified 1976 July 8) for Albert Lavine (d. 1967 August 13); letters from Wayne to Bureau of Vital Statistics, Hurley Wisconsin re birth certificate for Abe Lavine.
    - Ambivalence SA (Slide Sales), 1979, 1980, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      Includes: Letters and invoices for purchases of Wayne's slide cassette presentation on "The Dorothy Series"; brochure from Audio/Visual Unlimited (Hollywood, CA) on slide and filmstrip presentations; brochure, "Teacher's Guide: Art Work, Careers in the Arts"; clipping from unidentified classified ad for slide/Audio-Cassette of "The Dorothy Series" [ca. 1980]; photocopy of production notes for "The Dorothy Series."
    - Negatives: Dorothy docs, etc. ...NOT USED, 1923, no date (Box 105, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for "My Sweetie Went Away" by Roy Turk & Lou Handman (c1923); two 5 x 7 inch black and white negatives taped together, one with typed definition of the word "pogrom", the other an image of the Ellis Island Immigration Center building with caption, "Ellis Island--New York's Port of Entry."
    - Photographs used and unused from Family Archive, 1947, no date (Box 105, Folder 3)
      Two 11 x 14 inch black and white photographic enlargements, one of Dorothy Kline as a young girl (used in creating Wayne's print, "Report Card" from "The Dorothy Series"), and the other with two images of Dorothy at a "Bien Jolie Sales Convention" for sales representatives (used in creating Wayne's print, "Dorothy and the IRS" from "The Dorothy Series.")
    - Photographs used and unused from Family Archive, 1955, no date (Box 105, Folder 4)
      Contains one 11 x 14 inch black and white photographic enlargement of a Bien Jolie Sales & Executive Dinner (1955 November 26), and one 11 x 14 inch black and white negative of Dorothy Kline as a young girl.
    - June: Original Documents, 1930 June 27 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      Wayne's certificate of completion and admission to high school issued by the Board of Education of the City of Chicago, Avondale School, Grammar Department (1930 June 27.)
    - Dorothy: Original Documents, 1952, 1960, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      Contains: Marriage license for Wayne's parents, Abe Lavine and Dorothy A. Kline (1917 May 24), and their divorce decree (1952 December 3); obituaries of Wayne's mother, Dorothy Kline (Chicago Sun-Times, 1960 June 30; Los Angeles Herald- Express, no date.)
    - Photographs used and unused from Family Archive, 1914, 1920, 1924 no date (Box 105, Folder 12)
      Family documents, including: Dorothy Kline's certificate, "Palmer Method of Business Writing" (1914 January 21), used in creating Wayne's print, "Palmer Method" from "The Dorothy Series"; and Dorothy Kline's certificate of completion and admission to high school issued by the Board of Education of the City of Chicago, Ray School, Grammar Department (1914 January 30); Nathan Kline's [Dorothy's brother] certificate of completion and admission to high school issued by the Board of Education of the City of Chicago, Scott School, Grammar Department (1924 June 20); Nathan R. Kline Jr.'s Hyde Park High School diploma (issued 1920 June 25); 12 x 17 inch black and white photographic enlargement of full-length portrait of Nathan Kline [Wayne's maternal grandfather], used in creating Wayne's print, "Desire to Write" from "The Dorothy Series."
  - Subseries 3: Exhibits, 1959-2006
    This subseries includes correspondence regarding exhibitions of Wayne's work.
    - Arizona State, 1978-1991 (Box 205, Folder 25)
    - Armory Center for the Arts, 2005-2008 (Box 205, Folder 26)
    - Atlanta College of Art: Herstory Exhibition, 1987, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      Correspondents include: Lisa Tuttle (Gallery Director, Atlanta College of Art) re Wayne's inclusion of "Arriving" from "The Dorothy Series" in the touring exhibition, "American Herstory: Women and the U.S. Constitution"; Ofelia Garcia (President, Atlanta College of Art) re Wayne's honorary doctorate of fine arts and acceptance speech; also includes press releases and reviews about the exhibition.
    - Centre Pompidou: "Los Angeles 1955-1985", 2005-2006 (Box 205, Folder 27)
    - Cerritos Show Feb. 19, 1991 (Gail Jacobs), 1990, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Correspondents include: Gail Jacobs (Art Gallery Director, Cerritos Community College District) re Wayne's participation in 1991 Invitational exhibition; also includes announcements from recent exhibitions and information on artist, Sandra Rowe.
    - Charleston Heights Art Center, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Correspondents include: Patricia Harris (Gallery Director) re Wayne's participation in panel discussion, "Today's Woman: The Changing Image" at Charleston Heights Art Center's Clark Library, Las Vegas (1981 December 1.)
    - Claremont Colleges, 1979-1992 (Box 205, Folder 28)
    - Des Moines Art Center: Demetrion, Jim, 1980-1982 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Farnsworth Art Museum, 2010 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Fresno Art Museum's Council of 100, 2006 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Hunterdon Museum of Art, 2007 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Jack Ruthberg Fine Arts, 2005-2006 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - June's Saloon, 2005 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - LACMA 1999, 2000, 2001, 2001-2006 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - LACMA: Made in California 2000 Show (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - LACMA: November 1998 Show, 1959-1999 (Box 164, Folder 7, Folder 8)
    - Minneapolis College of Art, 1983-1984 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1994-2008 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - National Museum of Women in the Arts: Pomeroy, Jordana, 2009-2010 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Neuberger Museum, 1998-2004 (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Neuberger Retrospective Materials, 1969-1999 (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - New Orleans Museum, 2001-2002 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Palmer, Herb, 2003 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Portland Art Museum: Gilkay, Gordon, 1996-2006 (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Print Club of Philadelphia, 1980-2008 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Riverside Museum, 2008-2009 (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - Roski Arts and Science Award: Stein, Donna, 2009 (Box 206, Folder 17)
    - Sects in the City, 2007 (Box 206, Folder 18)
    - Sierra Nevada College, 1985 (Box 206, Folder 19)
    - Solway Jones Gallery, 2008-2009 (Box 206, Folder 20)
    - Southern California Women's Caucus for Art: Barnsdall Show, 2005-2007 (Box 206, Folder 21)
    - Stanford University of Art, 1992 (Box 206, Folder 22)
    - State University of New York at Albany: Bernstein, R., 1981-1983 (Box 206, Folder 25)
    - State University of New York at Albany: Fasulo, Marijo, 1983 (Box 206, Folder 26)
    - Stein, Donna, 1990-2009 (Box 206, Folder 23)
    - Steinbaum Gallery, 1993-2004 (Box 206, Folder 24)
    - State University of New York at Purchase, 1982 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Then and Now: Funkel, Bruria, 2006-2009 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - University of California, Los Angeles: Grunwald Center, Photo Loans, 1995 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Wack! Vancouver, 2009 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Westerman, Donna: Orange Coast College, 2009 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Zill, Anne, 2000 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Zimmer Children's Museum, 2008-2010 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 4: Fan Mail, 1968-1974
    This subseries includes cards, memos, and letters to Wayne and KCET, expressing opinions on Wayne's television series, "June Wayne" (1972-1973).
    - KCET Fan Mail (TV Series), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Cards, memos and letters to Wayne and KCET expressing opinions on Wayne's television series, "June Wayne" (1972-1973). Correspondents include: Los Angeles Civic Light Opera Association (Eleanor Pinkham); Jan Stussy (UCLA art instructor); Artists Equity Association (Molly Brylawski, executive secretary); Dorothy Dehner; Edgar Ewing; Lillian Paley; Whitney Museum of American Art (Elke Solomon, curator); Ethel Shapiro Bertolini; Society of American Graphic Artists (SAGA) (Martin Barooshian, president); Helen Aylon; UCLA Dickson Art Center Video Laboratory (Bob Jacobson, video committee); Rachel Rosenthal; Belle Osipow; Jill Giegerich; UCLA Frederick S. Wight Galleries (Frederick S. Wight, director); Ross-Freeman Gallery (Diane Ross, owner); Artists for Economic Action (Ron Blumberg, president.)
    - KCET TV Series (Fan Mail), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Cards, memos and letters to Wayne and KCET expressing opinions on Wayne's television series, "June Wayne" (1972-1973.) Correspondents include: Robert Bruce Rogers, including photograph and two R.B. Rogers print images; Fay Lansner; Martha Padve (Pasadena Museum of Art board member); Gilberto Lujan; biographical material about artist Toby Judith Klayman; Jane Besen (commissioner, Monterey Park Arts and Culture Commission.)
    - Sobanski, Lee, 1969, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 26)
      Includes letter about his poetry, and Sobanski's poem, "To June Wayne The Graphic Artist."
    - Sobanski, Lee, 1968 Apr (Box 105, Folder 5)
      Drawing (signed and dated) by Lee S. Sobanski of buildings from corner perspective, executed in ink on a paper towel.
  - Subseries 5: IRS, 1970-1997
    This subseries includes correspondence regarding the Internal Revenue Service's Revenue Ruling 79-256 on charitable contributions. Also included are Wayne's correspondence with attorney Marvin Goodson regarding Wayne's litigation with the Commercial Union Insurance Company and appraisals of her charitable contributions of art work (1970-1978).
    - Revenue Ruling 79-256, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Correspondents re IRS Revenue Ruling 79-256 on charitable contributions include: Elena Canavier [ceramicist, later known as Elena Karina]; James T. Demetrion (President, The Association of Art Museum Directors); Grace Glueck (New York Times); Milt Esterow (Editor & Publisher, Art News); Marshall M. Holleb (Holleb, Gerstein & Glass, Ltd, Attorneys at Law, Chicago, IL); Barbara Isenberg (theater writer and Los Angeles Times correspondent); James Melchart (National Endowment for the Arts); Joan A. Mondale (wife of Walter Mondale); Franklin Murphy (Times Mirror Company, Los Angeles, CA); William Norris (Tuttle & Taylor, Attorneys at Law, Los Angeles, CA); Max Palevsky (American art collector, venture capitalist, philanthropist, Malibu, CA); Senator Claiborne Pell (Rhode Island); Andrew Robison (Curator of Prints and Drawings, National Gallery of Art, Washington D.C.); Senator Alan Sieroty (California); Ben Smith (Beverly Hills, CA); David Steadman (Galleries of the Pomona Colleges, Claremont, CA); Congressman Frank Thompson, Jr.; Mary Ann Tighe (Deputy Chairman for Programs, National Endowment for the Arts, Washington D.C.); Marcia Weisman (collector of modern and contemporary art with husband, Frederick Weisman); Senator Harrison A. Williams, Jr. (New Jersey); Edith Wylie (Craft and Folk Museum, Los Angeles, CA); Congressman Sidney R. Yates; also includes newspaper clippings of articles by Herbert Mitgang, "Book Publishers See Peril To Old Stock in Tax Rule" (New York Times, 1980 September 3) and Michiko Kakutani, "Millions of Books Endangered as Result of Tax Ruling" (New York Times, 1980 October 5.)
    - Goodson, Marvin, 1981, 1983-1985, 1991-1994, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Correspondents include Marvin Goodson (Goodson and Wachtel Law Offices, Los Angeles, CA) re: Wayne's litigation with Commercial Union Insurance Company; acquisition of Judith A. Hoffberg collection of artists' books by University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA); Wayne's recommendations for print appraisers, Nancy Escher and Orrel P. Reed; description and appraisal of Wayne's "Songs and Sonets of John Donne" by Orrel P. Reed; revision of Wayne's Trust; copy of decision on Estate of Georgia T. O'Keeffe, Tax Court Memorandum Decisions (1992 April 16); Daniel Golubev re contact information for Dr. Jonas Salk; pages from the Los Angeles Times with article about Jonas Salk by Sheryl Stolberg, "Hero With Something to Prove" (1993 March 7); Wayne's letter to the editor of the Los Angeles Times re article on Dr. Salk; Wayne's gift of prints to the Neuberger Museum of Art (State University of New York, Purchase, NY.)
    - Goodson 1984 Summation + Case re IRS, 1970-1980, 1983, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Includes list of lithographs sold to Goldstein & Phillips, Counselors at Law (San Francisco, CA) as of 1980 January 20; list of Tamarind subscription prints (1970-1979); Disposition of works of art sold to June Wayne from Tamarind Subscription Collection (1974-1978); summaries of 1973-1979 collections of Tamarind Institute subscription; Fair Market Value of Tamarind Impressions lithographs gifted to Claremont Colleges (Claremont, CA) executed by O.P. Reed Jr., as of 1976 December 6; appraisals of Wayne's charitable contributions of art work, 1970, 1972-1978.
    - Goodson IRS Tax Court Case 76' 77' 78', 1972, 1977, 1978, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Includes Wall Street Journal clipping on artist, Gloria Churchman and Tax Court ruling (1977 August 17); Washington Post clipping of article by Paul Richard, "A Taxing Problem: How to Tax the Sculpture in David Smith's Estate" (1972 February 17); Wayne's original receipts for professional services (1978, 1980); Wayne's litigation with IRS and tax liability for 1976 and 1977; photocopy of Saturday Review article by Blake Fleetwood, "The Tax Police: Trampling Citizens' Rights" (1980 May); 30-Day Letters and IRS Examination Report (1980 November 25); correspondents include Marvin Goodson (attorney) re Wayne's IRS tax audit for 1976, 1977, and 1978.
  - Subseries 6: John Donne's Book, 1958-2009
    This subseries includes correspondence regarding the production of Wayne's book, "The Songs and Sonets of John Donne" (1983).
    - Brooks, Helen, 2008-2009 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Brooks, Helen, 2008-2010 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Donne Book: Inventory 908, 2008 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Donne Book: Making of, 1997 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - John Donne, 10-23-08: Bonnie Cashin Lecture, 2008 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - John Donne, 10-23-08: Invites, Drafts, 2008 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - John Donne, 10-23-08: Mailer, 2008 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - John Donne, 10-23-08: Programs, Fashion Event, 2008 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - John Donne, Cashin Event 2008: Paul Parrish, UCLA (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - John Donne, Cashin Event 2008: Maylee Witham (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - John Donne, Cashin 2-15-09: Drafts, Print Lists, 2009 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - John Donne, Cashin 10-23-09: V. Steele, 2009 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - John Donne: Journal, 2008-2009 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - John Donne Lecture: Jonathan F.S. Post, UCLA, 2-15-09, 2009 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - John Donne, Songs + Sonnets. Correspondence: Bruder Hartmann., 1958-1960 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Correspondents include: Kurt and Fritz Hartmann (Brüder Hartmann, Buchdruckerei [letterpress printing] Berlin- Schöneberg) re production and shipping of Wayne's book, "Songs and Sonets of John Donne"; Japanpapier Import Gessellschaft (Frankfurt) re Wayne's request for lithography paper for the book; Ernes Freed (Professor, Graphics Department, Los Angeles County Art Institute [interim name for Otis Art Institute]) re exchange exhibition of the Graphic Workshop of Pratt at the Art Institute; W. McNeil Lowry (Director, Program in Humanities and the Arts, Ford Foundation), William S. Lieberman (Curator, Department of Drawings, Museum of Modern Art, New York), Bertha von Moschzisker (Director, The Print Club, Philadelphia), Karl Kup (Curator of Prints, New York Public Library), and Una E. Johnson (Curator of Prints and Drawings, Brooklyn Museum of Art) re Wayne's visit to New York with "Songs and Sonets" book; also includes: shipping invoices from Schenker & Co. (Berlin) and Holland-Amerika Lijn (Rotterdam, Netherlands); black and white photographic postcard of Fritz and Barbara Hartmann at their wedding, with Fritz' father, Kurt Hartmann (1960)
    - John Donne, Songs + Sonnets. Correspondence: General., 1958-1961 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Correspondents include: R.B. Beaman (Exhibition Chairman, Carnegie Institute of Technology, Pittsburgh, PA) re borrowing about 12 of Wayne's prints for exhibition with Inez Johnston and Edmondson (reverse includes handwritten list of prints Wayne sent); Wayne to Westminster Recording Sales Corp. (New York, NY) and Music Masters (New York, NY) re acquiring copies of vinyl record album, "Poems by John Donne and William Wordsworth" read by Christopher Hassall; Ruth Feder; Mae [last name unknown]; Margery Nemeth, Sigmund and Florence Theil, and Anita and Leo Rangell re purchasing copy of Wayne's "Songs and Sonets"; Jake Zeitlin (Zeitlin & Ver Brugge Booksellers, Los Angeles, CA) to Theodore J.H. Gusten (Print Council of America) re distributing circulars on Wayne's John Donne portfolio to Print Council members; Zeitlin to Wayne re consignment copies of "Songs and Sonets"; also includes biographical material [in English and French, written by Pierre Courthion] on Wayne for promotion of her book, "Songs and Sonets of John Donne"; list of names to be printed on "Songs and Sonets" dedication page.
    - John Donne, Songs + Sonnets. Correspondence: E. Lustig Cohen, G. Braziller, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Correspondents include: Elaine Lustig Cohen (graphic designer) re Kono mask, layout and production of Wayne's "Songs and Sonets of John Donne", American printers, Hartmann in Berlin; George Braziller, Inc. (New York, NY) re production agreement of "Songs and Sonets."
    - John Donne, Songs + Sonnets Subscribers, 1958, 1960, 1961, 1974, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Correspondents re replacement covers and purchases of Wayne's "Songs and Sonets of John Donne" include: Dr. Elmer Belt; Alexander M. Bing; Jerome Allan Dodson (Long Beach Museum of Art) re order for Doris Maxwell; Ebria Feinblatt (Curator of Prints and Drawings, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Los Angeles, CA); Meyer Flax (Flax Art Supplies, Westwood); Fred Grunwald; Jack and Fran Harrison; Brüder Hartman (Berlin, German); John Howell; Warren R. Howell; Deborah A. Hughes; Dr. Benjamin M. Jurin; Dr. and Mrs. John C. Mergener; Dr. Lester M. Morrison; Gifford Philips; Chief Librarian, Reed College Bookstore (Portland, OR); Helen and Josephus Reynolds; Albert Roncey re receiving artist's proof print and copy of "Songs and Sonets" for Baron Edmond Adolphe Maurice Jules Jacques de Rothschild (1926-1997) on the occasion of the baron's marriage (1958 November 4) to Veselinka Vladova Gueorguieva; Benjamin B. Smith; Dr. A.M. Targow; Philip Wain; Dr. Milton Wexler; Yale Wexler (Wexler Brothers Productions); also includes list of subscribers for Wayne's "Songs and Sonets of John Donne" and names for the book's nominative (dedication) page.
    - John Donne, Songs + Sonnets Invoices, 1959-1963, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Invoices for sales of Wayne's "Songs and Sonets of John Donne" to: Mrs. Moore S. Achenbach; Mrs. Miki Benoff; Alexander M. Bing; Jane Darvin; Daniel and Ruth Feder; Fred Grunwald; Mr. and Mrs. Felix Juda; Dr. Benjamin Jurin; Mr. and Mrs. Edgar Kadden; Gladys Kaufman; Lewis Kaufman; Mrs. Alvin Kleeb; Karl Kup (Curator of Prints, New York Public Library); Dr. and Mrs. Milton Lane; Los Angeles County Museum of Art; Abe Lubin; Samuel Lustgarten; Doris Maxwell; Dr. and Mrs. John C. Mergener; Dr. and Mrs. Milton Miller; Dr. Lester M. Morrison; Margery Nemeth; Ruth and Harry Nierenberg; Dr. and Mrs. Aaron Nisenson; Rochelle Orchard; Agnes Plumb; Dr. Marcus H. Rabwin; Anita and Leo Rangell; Dan Rosen; Halina and Bernard Rosenthal; Allan P. Sindler; Ben and Dorothy Smith; Dr. Philip Solomon; Dr. A.M. Targow; Dr. Helen Tausend; Mr. and Mrs. Sig Theil; Mr. and Mrs. Philip Wain; Dr. Milton Wexler; Yale Wexler; Zeitlin & Ver Brugge.
    - John Donne, Songs + Sonnets Public Collections, Libraries., 1958, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Correspondents re replacement covers and purchases of Wayne's "Songs and Sonets of John Donne" include: Mrs. Moore S. Achenbach; Jenx Nyholm (Northwestern University Library, Evanton, IL); Robert Honeyman, Jr.; Frank S. Hanlin (Head, Acquisitions Department, State University of Iowa, Iowa City, IA); Mrs. P.B. Haga (Acquisitions Department, University of Minnesota Library, Minneapolis, MN); Wilkie Foundation (Des Plaines, IL); Zeitlin & Ver Brugge; also includes list of names and addresses of subscribers.
    - John Donne: "Friends of English", 2008-2009 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - John Donne: "Friends of English" Invite Info 2-15-09, 2009 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 7: Legislation, 1973-2011
    This subseries includes correspondence regarding a zoning amendment to the Los Angeles Municipal Code, and Wayne's statement presented at a public hearing (1981) in support of the amendment. Also includes correspondence from Artists for Tax Equity and various U.S. and California state senators regarding Section 263(A) of the Internal Revenue Code of 1986 and Assembly Bill 1054.
    - Art Organizations and Workshops AB1054, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 18)